<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SELF DEFENSE on IMORTANCE OF SELF DEFENCE</title>
    <link>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/tags/self-defense/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SELF DEFENSE on IMORTANCE OF SELF DEFENCE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 03:52:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://km.harinandanp.xyz/tags/self-defense/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Krav Maga Techniques</title>
      <link>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-vidoes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2020 03:52:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-vidoes/</guid>
      <description>Krav MAGA   Knife attack defense   Stick attack defense   Back grabs   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Self-Defense Training</title>
      <link>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 21:52:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>The Ability To Defend Yourself And Your Loved Ones The most important aspect of self-defense training and, really, it’s primary purpose. By training, you prepare your mind and body to respond to threats against your safety or your life. The truth in today’s society is that help is not always available in time to make a difference. When under the pressure of a stressful situation, especially an attack or survival situation, people automatically revert to what they’ve practiced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History of Krav Maga</title>
      <link>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-second-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 16:52:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-second-post/</guid>
      <description>Translated literally as “close combat”, Krav Maga originated in Czechoslovakia in the 1930’s, primarily by Imi Lichtenfeld to protect his people from brutalization in Pre-World War II Europe. Lichtenfeld grew up in an increasingly tough neighborhood and dealt regularly with thugs, violent gangs and anti-Semites. On these tough streets, Krav Maga was born as Lichtenfeld began to combine different techniques to form an effective, simple approach to self-defense for the Jewish community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals and basic principles</title>
      <link>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-third-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2020 11:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-third-post/</guid>
      <description>There are no rules for Krav Maga fighting. Men and women generally undergo the same drills, it has no sporting federation, and there are no official uniforms or attire. One basic principle of Krav Maga is to redirect the opponent’s own strength to put him at a disadvantage. Every joint in the body is designed to bend a specific way, and by forcing it in the other direction, it snaps. Size has little impact on how effective a fighter is due to the method of continuing an opponent’s momentum to add to the velocity of a strike, force a throw or to create separation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-fourth-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 10:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://km.harinandanp.xyz/posts/my-fourth-post/</guid>
      <description>Endurance Endurance can be looked at in a couple of different ways, mainly physical endurance and mental endurance. When you learn Krav Maga you will develop endurance in both aspects.Physical endurance is developed and reinforced in your body in the same way that muscles are built in your body. If you make your muscles do something they aren’t used to, aka apply a resistance to them, they will reach a point where they fail.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
